Guide to the Records of American Association for Ethiopian Jews (AAEJ), undated, 1960-1961, 1963, 1965-1968, 1970-1995, 2001-2002 *I-503
American Jewish Historical Society, Boston, MA and New York, NY
- Subgroup II: AAEJ Activists, undated, 1961, 1963, 1966, 1968, 1970-1993; Boxes 38-139.
  - Series A: LaDena Schnapper (AAEJ Coordinator) Files, undated, 1961, 1963, 1966, 1968, 1970-1991; Boxes 38-120.
    - Subseries 2: Schnapper Rescue and Relief, undated, 1968, 1970-1991; Boxes 42-89.
      - Subsubseries a: Rescue and Relief A-Z, undated, 1970-1991; Boxes 42-65.
        - Aragaw Nega, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 8)
        - Aragaw Zeleke, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 9)
        - Aragew Esayes, undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
        - Aregaw Chole, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 11)
        - Asaye Melkie, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 12)
        - Asedesach Derso, 1989-1990 (Box 44, Folder 13)
        - Asefa Eyob, 1986, 1988-1989 (Box 44, Folder 14)
        - Asegedeth Chanie, 1988-1989 (Box 44, Folder 15)
        - Aseresse Belay, undated, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 16)
        - Asfaw Robel, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 17)
        - Asfawossen Alemseged, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 18)
        - Asimare Dawit, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 19)
        - Asimare Takele, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 20)
        - Asmamaw Addisu, 1987-1988 (Box 44, Folder 21)
        - Asmamaw Bayuh, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 22)
        - Asmara Biru, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 23)
        - Asmare Eneyu, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 24)
        - Asmare Getie, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 25)
        - Asmaru Yimer, 1988-1989 (Box 44, Folder 26)
        - Asnakew Eyasu, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 27)
        - Asrat Sinke, 1985-1986 (Box 44, Folder 28)
        - Asresie Teferie, 1987, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 29)
        - Asressie Mengiste, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 30)
        - Asreste Abate, 1981, 1989-1990 (Box 44, Folder 31)
        - Assef Ferede Family, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 32)
        - Assefa Aarone, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 33)
        - Assefa Belay, 1988-1989 (Box 44, Folder 34)
        - Assefa Dawit, 1989-1990 (Box 44, Folder 35)
        - Assefa Tega, 1987-1990 (Box 44, Folder 36)
        - Assenaku Mengeste, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 37)
        - Aster Awaju, 1989-1990 (Box 44, Folder 38)
        - Aster Kidane, 1986-1987 (Box 44, Folder 39)
        - Atanaw Meshesha, 1988-1989 (Box 44, Folder 40)
        - Atlabachew Assefa, 1989-1990 (Box 44, Folder 41)
        - Atsede Yimer's Niece, Nephew Bethlehem Girma, 1972, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 42)
        - Avaro Abraham (Yefet Zauda Family), 1987-1988 (Box 44, Folder 43)
        - Avaro Adyo, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 44)
        - Avata Adgo, 1982, 1989-1990 (Box 44, Folder 45)
        - Awoke Engdaw, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 46)
        - Awoke Sibhat, 1986-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1)
        - Ayanaw Belay, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 2)
        - Ayanaw Demozie, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 3)
        - Ayehu Feheta, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 4)
        - Ayele Eshete, 1988, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 5)
        - Ayele Tega, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 6)
        - Ayelegn Barkew Family (contains photograph), undated, 1981-1982, 1987-1989 (Box 45, Folder 7)
        - Ayelign Alebachew, undated, 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 8)
        - Ayelign Chekolle, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 9)
        - Ayenew Berihun, 1982, 1988-1989 (Box 45, Folder 10)
        - Ayenew Tebeje, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 11)
        - Aylegn Mekonen, undated, 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 12)
        - Ayou Yehulashet Wassie, undated, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 13)
        - Azanaw Ayalew (empty folder) (Box 45, Folder 14)
        - Azanaw Azezew Betewling, 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 15)
        - Azanaw Nega, 1987, 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 16)
        - Azenu Adane, 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 17)
        - Azzeb Aberra, 1988-1989 (Box 45, Folder 18)
        - Banchayehu Nega, undated, 1986-1987 (Box 45, Folder 19)
        - Baruch Fordu, undated, 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 20)
        - Baruch Gete's Family, 1986-1988 (Box 45, Folder 21)
        - Baruch Tegegne's Family, undated, 1986-1988 (Box 45, Folder 22)
        - Baruch Teka, 1985, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 23)
        - Baush Abraham, 1986-1987 (Box 45, Folder 24)
        - Baye Negash, 1982, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 25)
        - Bayeh Fisseha, 1980, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 26)
        - Bayleyegne Mangistu (Captain), 1987-1989 (Box 45, Folder 27)
        - Baynesagne Eniew / Sudan, 1985, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 28)
        - Bayu Terefe Family, 1988-1989 (Box 45, Folder 29)
        - Bayuh Mehari, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 30)
        - Bayush Solomon, undated, 1981-1982, 1988-1990 (Box 45, Folder 31)
        - Bayush Takele, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 32)
        - Bazeto Bogale, 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 33)
        - Behon Yekiye, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 34)
        - Bekele Alene, 1982, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 35)
        - Belay Zaudu Zemu, 1980, 1988-1989 (Box 45, Folder 36)
        - Belayneh Tsegaye, 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 37)
        - Belete Admas, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 38)
        - Beletech Wondemagne, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 39)
        - Berehane Mengistu, 1970, 1974, 1985, 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 40)
        - Berhan Alem, 1987-1990 (Box 46, Folder 1)
        - Berhanu Amboy (empty folder) (Box 46, Folder 2)
        - Berhanu Feradu, 1987-1990 (Box 46, Folder 3)
        - Berhanu Yiradu (contains photographs), undated, 1973, 1980, 1982-1990 (Box 46, Folder 4)
        - Berhanu Zelleke, 1981, 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 5)
        - Berihun Moges, 1981-1982, 1989-1990 (Box 46, Folder 6)
        - Berke Gebregiogis, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 7)
        - Bertukan Dessie (Tesfahum Baruk Family), 1989 (Box 46, Folder 8)
        - Bertukan Lakia, Tesfu Wubet, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 9)
        - Betaha Molla, Eshete Molla (empty folder) (Box 46, Folder 10)
        - Betashalame Abetu, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 11)
        - Betecha Alemie, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 12)
        - Betelhem Afework, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 13)
        - Betetanesh Taddese, undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
        - Betha Fereda, 1989-1990 (Box 46, Folder 15)
        - Betty Abebe, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 16)
        - Bewketu Addela, Berchecho Dawit, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 17)
        - Bewkete Adela, 1989-1990 (Box 46, Folder 18)
        - Beyan Alyi, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 19)
        - Beyene Demozie, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 20)
        - Beyene Mengiste, 1984-1985, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 21)
        - Beyene Mengistu, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 22)
        - Beyene Negussie, 1987-1988 (Box 46, Folder 23)
        - Bezuneh Aychilutim / Erstu's brother, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 24)
        - Bicha Solomon, Altush Asnakew, undated, 1978, 1985-1990 (Box 46, Folder 25)
        - Bilelegn Alene, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 26)
        - Birchiko Eyasu (empty folder) (Box 46, Folder 27)
        - Birhanu Tarekegne, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 28)
        - Birke Zelleke (empty folder) (Box 46, Folder 29)
        - Biruk Asfaw, 1980, 1988-1989 (Box 46, Folder 30)
        - Bitew Melkamu, undated, 1983, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 31)
        - Biyazeneigne Alehegne, 1987-1989 (Box 46, Folder 32)
        - Bizezaw Taffera, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 33)
        - Chaim Negist's Family Bideglelegne Negussie, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 34)
        - Chaklit Nega, undated, 1987-1989 (Box 46, Folder 35)
        - Chaklu Aron, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 36)
        - Chale Getahun Family, 1988-1989 (Box 46, Folder 37)
        - Chane Adamasu's Family, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 38)
        - Chane Yeshayahu's Family, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 39)
        - Chanie Tewabe, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 40)
        - Chekole Tewabe, 1989-1990 (Box 46, Folder 41)
        - Dagnew Belew, 1978, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 42)
        - Daniel Alebachew, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 43)
        - Daniel Darge, 1989-1990 (Box 46, Folder 44)
        - Daniel Lisanu Beyene, 1989-1990 (Box 46, Folder 45)
        - Daniel Meleka Hiwist, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 46)
        - Daniel Mengistu, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 1)
        - David Tessema's Family, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 47, Folder 2)
        - David Wotes Children - Zahava Koku, Cassaye Ayele, undated, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 3)
        - Dawit Gola, undated, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 4)
        - Dawit Family (Wube, Abuhay, etc.), 1987 (Box 47, Folder 5)
        - Dawit Fekede (empty folder) (Box 47, Folder 6)
        - Dawit Tegegne, 1989-1990 (Box 47, Folder 7)
        - Degan Estubdink, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 8)
        - Degitu Acheneke, 1989-1990 (Box 47, Folder 9)
        - Deman Yalew, 1988-1989 (Box 47, Folder 10)
        - Demelash Aysheshim, 1985, 1988-1989 (Box 47, Folder 11)
        - Demelash Yigazaw, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 12)
        - Demoz Aderagew, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 13)
        - Demozie Dessie, 1988-1989 (Box 47, Folder 14)
        - Dennekew Asaye, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 15)
        - Densa Dawit, Erkaye Ezra, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 16)
        - Derbe Melkae, 1982, 1989-1990 (Box 47, Folder 17)
        - Dereba Tarekegne, 1987-1988 (Box 47, Folder 18)
        - Derebe Takele (empty folder) (Box 47, Folder 19)
        - Derebe Tilahoun, 1977, 1985-1987 (Box 47, Folder 20)
        - Derebie Alemayehaw, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 21)
        - Derese Lakew, 1981, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 22)
        - Derso Dessie, 1988-1989 (Box 47, Folder 23)
        - Derso (Tesfa) Family, undated (Box 47, Folder 24)
        - Desalegne Alemneh, 1980-1981, 1988-1990 (Box 47, Folder 25)
        - Dessalegn, Alemeneh, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 26)
        - Dessalegn Ayalew, 1980, 1987-1989 (Box 47, Folder 27)
        - Dessalegn Eyob, undated, 1978, 1984-1990 (Box 47, Folder 28)
        - Dessalegn Eyob's Family, undated, 1979, 1986-1990 (Box 47, Folder 29)
        - Dessalegn Gebeyehu Kinde, 1978, 1986-1989 (Box 47, Folder 30)
        - Dessalegn Gedimon, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 31)
        - Desalegne Melkamu, undated, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 32)
        - Dessalegn Tarakegne's Family, 1988-1989 (Box 47, Folder 33)
        - Dessie Andargaghew, undated (Box 47, Folder 34)
        - Dessie Meshesha, 1987-1988 (Box 47, Folder 35)
        - Dessie Mihret, 1987, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 36)
        - Dessie Sebhat Ferede, 1989-1990 (Box 47, Folder 37)
        - Dessie Tekuye, 1987-1989 (Box 47, Folder 38)
        - Dessie Yohannes, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 39)
        - Desta Asresse, undated, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 40)
        - Desta Mengistu, 1970, 1980, 1983-1984, 1986-1990 (Box 48, Folder 1)
        - Devere Tegegne, 1988-1989 (Box 48, Folder 2)
        - Devorah Melesse, 1989-1990 (Box 48, Folder 3)
        - Dinbulu Mehretu Jember, 1982, 1989-1990 (Box 48, Folder 4)
        - Dinku Ferede, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 5)
        - Diress Tafere, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 6)
        - Efraim Enyew Milkie - Sudan, 1986, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 7)
        - Ejigu Amene, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 8)
        - Eleni Tadesse, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 9)
        - Eli Mengistu Family, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 10)
        - Eliahu Teshager Family, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 11)
        - Elias Ermias, 1988-1989 (Box 48, Folder 12)
        - Elias Mengistu, 1989-1990 (Box 48, Folder 13)
        - Elias Zewdu, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 14)
        - Elifiachew Baheru, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 15)
        - Elizabeth Sabere, 1976, 1988-1990 (Box 48, Folder 16)
        - Elsa Mitku, 1985-1986 (Box 48, Folder 17)
        - Else Aboy, undated, 1980, 1987-1989 (Box 48, Folder 18)
        - Else Sinke / Haile's mother, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 19)
        - Emabat Kidana, 1989-1990 (Box 48, Folder 20)
        - Emabet Ambaw, 1989-1990 (Box 48, Folder 21)
        - Emabet Zeizanu (empty folder) (Box 48, Folder 22)
        - Emebet Asmare, undated, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 23)
        - Emebet Belay, undated, 1981, 1987, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 24)
        - Emebet Orion, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 25)
        - Embet Alemu, undated (Box 48, Folder 26)
        - Emuhay Mesosha, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 27)
        - Enanu Mulu, 1981-1982, 1988-1989 (Box 48, Folder 28)
        - Enanu Zewdie, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 29)
        - Enaye Achenua, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 30)
        - Endalew Abagaz, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 31)
        - Endalew Abegaz, 1981, 1986, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 32)
        - Endalew Adella, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 33)
        - Endalew Alebachew, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 34)
        - Endalew Tilahun Family, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 35)
        - Eneye Tizazu, undated, 1980-1982, 1988-1989 (Box 48, Folder 36)
        - Eneyesh Fereda, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 37)
        - Eneyesh Yoseph, 1981, 1987-1989 (Box 48, Folder 38)
        - Eneyew Sendeke, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 39)
        - England Family Papers, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 40)
        - Enyew Asefa, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 41)
        - Enquayemosh Reday, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 42)
        - Ertibu Melkias, undated, 1989-1990 (Box 48, Folder 43)
        - Esayas Muche, 1989-1990 (Box 48, Folder 44)
        - Eshetayehu Bayeh, 1981, 1987-1989 (Box 48, Folder 45)
        - Eshete Akale, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 48, Folder 46)
        - Eshete Aron, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 47)
        - Eshete Mogus, Woggera Relief, 1987-1990 (Box 49, Folder 1)
        - Eshete Tilahun, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 2)
        - Eshetu Barkew, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 3)
        - Eshetu Ezineh, 1988-1989 (Box 49, Folder 4)
        - Eshetu Kebede, undated, 1971-1972, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 5)
        - Estefinos Yasu, undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
        - Etanesh Melesse, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 7)
        - Etye Mehari, 1979, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 8)
        - Etsubdenk Wonbagen, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 9)
        - Eyasu Makonen, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 10)
        - Eyasu Makonnen, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 11)
        - Eyayou Negatu, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 12)
        - Eyayu Asayehegn, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 13)
        - Eyerusalem Negussie, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 14)
        - Eyeyew Bekele, undated, 1981, 1989-1990 (Box 49, Folder 15)
        - Eyeyew Esayeyas Eshetu, undated, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 16)
        - Ezera Mamo (Berhane Zelleke), 1986 (Box 49, Folder 17)
        - Fantanesh Zenebe, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 18)
        - Fantu Mekete (Layew Sisay), 1980, 1988-1989 (Box 49, Folder 19)
        - Feit, Joe, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 20)
        - Fekade Mulugeta, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 21)
        - Fekadu Tarekegne, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 22)
        - Fekede Lemma, 1988-1989 (Box 49, Folder 23)
        - Felegne Tamayeit Family (empty folder) (Box 49, Folder 24)
        - Felegu Takele, 1988-1991 (Box 49, Folder 25)
        - Fenote - Israel Atnafu, 1989-1990 (Box 49, Folder 26)
        - Fenta Mehretu, 1989-1990 (Box 49, Folder 27)
        - Fentahun Assefa's Family, Assefa Dawit, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 28)
        - Fentahun Degif - Sudan, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 29)
        - Fentahun Malaku (empty folder) (Box 49, Folder 30)
        - Fentahun Mehari, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 31)
        - Fentahun Tezazu, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 32)
        - Fentanes Gonte, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 33)
        - Fentanesh Abebe, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 34)
        - Fentanesh Redai, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 35)
        - Fentanshe Ashagrie, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 36)
        - Fentaye Alesaw, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 37)
        - Fentaye Birru, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 38)
        - Fente Simon, 1986-1988 (Box 49, Folder 39)
        - Fente Simon, Amisal Mengiste, undated, 1985-1989 (Box 49, Folder 40)
        - Fentu Mekete, 1987-1989 (Box 49, Folder 41)
        - Ferehiwat Yishak, 1972, 1989-1990 (Box 49, Folder 42)
        - Fesseha Miheret Askias, undated, 1980, 1985-1990 (Box 49, Folder 43)
        - Fetegy Yishak, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 44)
        - Fikere Tiruneh, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 45)
        - Fikre Selassie Wogdaresh, undated (Box 49, Folder 46)
        - Fikre Tiruneh Selam, 1987-1989 (Box 49, Folder 47)
        - Fisseha Kalev, 1989-1990 (Box 49, Folder 48)
        - Fitige Kebede, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 1)
        - Fitigie Mekuanint Tamrat, 1986-1989 (Box 50, Folder 2)
        - Gebayew Chole, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 3)
        - Gebechew Alem, 1980, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 4)
        - Gebeyanesh Negussie, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 5)
        - Gebeya Melesse, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 6)
        - Gebeye Melesse, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 7)
        - Gebeyehu Kinde, 1982, 1988-1989 (Box 50, Folder 8)
        - Gebeyhu Semanie (empty folder) (Box 50, Folder 9)
        - Gebeyenesh Lakew, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 10)
        - Genet Hailu, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 11)
        - Genet Shiferaw, 1988-1989 (Box 50, Folder 12)
        - Genetu Ayelyn, 1986-1987, 1989-1990 (Box 50, Folder 13)
        - Genetu Tessema (contains photographs), undated, 1980, 1985-1990 (Box 50, Folder 14)
        - Genzeb Mahry, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 15)
        - Getachew Alem, 1989-1990 (Box 50, Folder 16)
        - Getachew Siraw, 1978, 1986, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 17)
        - Getachew Siraw, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 18)
        - Getahun Bicha, undated, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 19)
        - Getahoun Degresse children, undated, 1984-1990 (Box 50, Folder 20-21)
        - Getahun Deresse kids, 1988-1990 (Box 50, Folder 22)
        - Getahun Malaku, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 23)
        - Getahun Mamo, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 24)
        - Getahun Mamo, 1987-1988 (Box 50, Folder 25)
        - Getahun Tilahun, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 26)
        - Gete Abraham, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 27)
        - Gete Sebhet / Sebehat(?), 1990 (Box 50, Folder 28)
        - Getenet Maaza, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 29)
        - Getinet Abera, undated, 1988-1990 (Box 50, Folder 30)
        - Getu Baruk, undated, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 31)
        - Getu Tefere's Family, undated, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 32)
        - Getu Yitsak, undated, 1987-1989 (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - Getu Wube, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 2)
        - Getu Zemene, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 3)
        - Gezae Haile, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 4)
        - Ghannatu Tenaw, 1979-1980, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 5)
        - Girma Hailu (contains photograph), 1979-1980, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 6)
        - Girma Moges (contains photograph), 1982, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 7)
        - Girmay Samuel, undated, 1986-1987, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 8)
        - Gobeze Achenefe's children, undated, 1986-1989 (Box 51, Folder 9)
        - Gobeze Dawite, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 10)
        - Gobeze Etsubdenk Family, undated, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 11)
        - Godadew Alemu, 1986-1990 (Box 51, Folder 12)
        - Godadit Tegnyne, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 13)
        - Grazmatch Woldu, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 14)
        - Guday Tegnye, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 15)
        - Haile Assefa Lemma, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 16)
        - Haile Kebede, undated, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 17)
        - Hailu Areni, undated, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 18)
        - Haim Baynesagen, 1985, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 19)
        - Hana Dawit's Family, Amaretch Yasu, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 20)
        - Haragu Adhamom / Kibret Berhan, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 21)
        - Haregwain Gete, undated, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 22)
        - Hezkiyas Ayalew, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 23)
        - Hidega Tiku, undated (Box 51, Folder 24)
        - Hiwot Sisay, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 25)
        - Hiwot Sitataw Bizuneh, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 26)
        - Ingidushet Haile, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 27)
        - Ishak Miniwab Tedda, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 28)
        - Iskinder Hapte, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 29)
        - Itayew Adane, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 30)
        - Iyenaw Mamunie (killed in Debark) (empty folder) (Box 51, Folder 31)
        - Jacob Alelegne Family, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 32)
        - Jegne Teggne, undated, 1986-1990 (Box 51, Folder 33)
        - Jember Mebrate, 1982, 1986, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 34)
        - Josef Abraham, undated, 1985-1990 (Box 51, Folder 35)
        - Kafele Tamayeit (empty folder) (Box 51, Folder 36)
        - Kassa Ferede, undated, 1979, 1986-1989 (Box 51, Folder 37)
        - Kassa Ferede Family - Bemayush Belay Parents, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 38)
        - Kassa Semu Family, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 39)
        - Kassahun Abebe, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 1)
        - Kassahun Mamo/Teruwork Asmelash, undated, 1980, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 2)
        - Kassahun Tegegne, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 3)
        - Kassanish Wube, 1986-1987 (Box 52, Folder 4)
        - Kassaye Belay, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 5)
        - Kassaye Mehari (empty folder) (Box 52, Folder 6)
        - Kassye Tizazu's Family, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 7)
        - Keleb Ereda, 1988-1989 (Box 52, Folder 8)
        - Kelebe Alemu, undated, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 9)
        - Kenaw Melkie (contains photograph), 1987-1989 (Box 52, Folder 10)
        - Kenedy Tequma, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 11)
        - Kenu Mekuanent, 1985-1987 (Box 52, Folder 12)
        - Kibret Alemu, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 13)
        - Kibur Tekle Eyasu, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 14)
        - Kifle Tesfagiogis, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 15)
        - Kinde Chole's Family, undated, 1987, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 16)
        - Kinde Malaku, Seblewengel Yirga, 1986-1990 (Box 52, Folder 17)
        - Koke Tsehaye, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 18)
        - Kokie Tirunhe, 1986-1989 (Box 52, Folder 19)
        - Kolu Sebhat, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 20)
        - Lake Tamrat, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 21)
        - Lakew Mesfin Tamrat, 1986-1990 (Box 52, Folder 22)
        - Layew Sendeke, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 23)
        - Legassa Zari, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 24)
        - Lemlem Mehari Denku, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 25)
        - Lemlem Molla Minieab, 1975, 1985-1986 (Box 52, Folder 26)
        - Leul Adugna, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 27)
        - Lijalem Seife, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 28)
        - Lule Aberra, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 29)
        - Lulu Bazie, undated, 1980, 1985, 1987-1989 (Box 52, Folder 30)
        - Makonnen Berhanu, 1985-1986 (Box 52, Folder 31)
        - Makonnen Eyasu, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 32)
        - Makuria Tsegaye, 1985-1987 (Box 52, Folder 33)
        - Malaku Belay, 1986, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 34)
        - Malaku Mequanint, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 35)
        - Malaku Taminu, 1986, 1988-1989 (Box 52, Folder 36)
        - Malaku Wolde, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 37)
        - Malede Ayele, 1986, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 1)
        - Mallede Ayanaw, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 2)
        - Mamo Ayalew, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 3)
        - Mamo Zeleke, undated, 1981, 1987-1989 (Box 53, Folder 4)
        - Manalabesh Asres, 1988-1989 (Box 53, Folder 5)
        - Manaleb Desta, undated, 1982, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 6)
        - Mancheldash Kassie Engeda, 1988 (Box 53, Folder 7)
        - Mantegbosh Aybsagne Kinfu, 1985-1986 (Box 53, Folder 8)
        - Mare Getahun, 1988 (Box 53, Folder 9)
        - Marie Assefa, 1987-1989 (Box 53, Folder 10)
        - Markos Desta w/ Gabriel, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 11)
        - Maru Begashaw, 1987, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 12)
        - Maru Makonnen, 1979-1980, 1988-1990 (Box 53, Folder 13)
        - Maru Muche, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 14)
        - Mary Mequanent, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 15)
        - Mebrat Yekove (empty folder) (Box 53, Folder 16)
        - Medhanie W. Woldemichael, undated, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 17)
        - Medhabnie Wolday, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 18)
        - Megeb Milkie, 1987-1988 (Box 53, Folder 19)
        - Megiste Asresse / Ayalneh, Tesfuneh, undated, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 20)
        - Mehari Abraha, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 21)
        - Mehari Aymelak, undated, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 22)
        - Mehari Robel cases, 1988-1989 (Box 53, Folder 23)
        - Mehari Zelleke (empty folder) (Box 53, Folder 24)
        - Meheret Mehari, undated, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 25)
        - Meherete Ayele Teka, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 26)
        - Meherete Ferede, 1977, 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 27)
        - Meherite Reddie, 1986-1990 (Box 53, Folder 28)
        - Mehrate Mehari, 1971, 1985-1986, 1988 (Box 53, Folder 29)
        - Mehretu Melkamu, undated, 1985, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 30)
        - Mekanent Tegaw, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 31)
        - Mekebeb Mehret, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 32)
        - Mekuant Mehari, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 33)
        - Mekonen Alemayew, 1988 (Box 53, Folder 34)